# Jude Lim (Ken Yoong)

# **MS in Computer Science and Applications**

Email: LinkedIn:

lkyoong428@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/jude-lim-9a2612101/

Mobile: Github

+1703-679-0990 https://github.com/KenLim4337/

Location: Portfolio:

Falls Church, VA https://kenlim4337.github.io/

Experienced front-end developer with over 3 years of industry experience working in web projects for a variety of clients. Currently a master's student in Computer Science and Applications at Virginia Tech with a focus in Human Computer Interaction, Data Analytics and Machine Learning. Passionate about developing and designing interfaces that put the user first.

### Skills

#### **Hard Skills**

Front End Web Development, Conversion Rate Optimization, Responsive Web Design, User Acceptance Testing, A/B Testing, Web Analytics, Back End Web Development, User Experience

#### **Soft Skills**

Teamwork, Problem Solving, Attention to Detail, Critical Thinking, Verbal Communication, Written Communication, Adaptability

#### **Technologies**

Web Technologies - HTML, CSS, SASS, LESS, Javascript, jQuery, React, Django, PHP Data and Analytics - MySQL, PostgreSQL, R, Python, Google Analytics, Google Tag Manager A/B Testing - Optimizely, VWO, Oracle Maxymizer, Google Optimize, AB Tasty Design Tools - Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, Invision, Figma, Balsamiq Other Programming Languages - Java, C#, C, Python Version Control - Git, Subversion

#### Languages

 $\label{eq:continuous} English (\textit{Native}), Mandarin (\textit{Intermediate}), Cantonese (\textit{Intermediate}), Bahasa \\ Melayu (\textit{Intermediate})$ 

### Education

### 2021 - Current

Master of Science in Computer Science and Applications, Virginia Tech

#### 2014 - 2017

Bachelor of Information Technology (Honors), University of Queensland

## Professional Experience

#### Frontend Developer (Conversion Rate Optimization)

February 2018 - July 2021

Conversion Kings (Australia) | Full-time

Increased conversion rates and revenue for over 40 national and international brands through the development, maintenance and analysis of over 250 A/B tests and web-pages.

- Developed pixel-perfect, responsive, cross-browser A/B tests and web-pages based on prototypes provided by designers.
- Reduced project turnaround time and missed bugs by 30% within the first half-year by implementing a standardized user acceptance testing process and managing the team surrounding it.
- Slashed training times for various processes by 50% by writing manuals to help on-board new team members.

### **Frontend Developer**

March 2020 - May 2020

Dance Sydney (Australia) | Freelance

Designed and developed a cross-browser, fully responsive video player used to deliver online dance courses to users.

#### **Frontend Developer**

March 2017 - November 2017

Gliding Queensland (Australia) | Freelance

Constructed a framework for the client's redesign efforts by providing feedback based on design and development best practices.

- Fixed existing issues and compiled recommended updates based on user experience principles.
- Documented website functions to help existing members easily access and modify published content.

#### **Teaching Assistant**

**April 2017 - October 2017** 

Code Camp (Australia) | Casual

Cooperated with other team members to deliver engaging and organized coding lessons to primary school children. The lessons were delivered on-schedule and well-received by both children and parents.

#### Intern

December 2015 - February 2016

KPerak Implementation and Coordination Corporation (Malaysia) | Full Time

Delivered a full-stack project in the form of an internal employee assessment web application. The project was completed 2 weeks ahead of schedule and subsequently deployed with minimal rework.

## Other Experience

**Hacker & Crew** 

**July 2017** 

GovHack 2017 (Australia)

Received honorable mention for the "Going places" national award category by developing a mobile web application. Also made sure participants were hacking in a safe and comfortable environment by helping set up the event location, providing technical support and preparing meals.

Hacker July 2016

GovHack 2016 (Australia)

Won runner-up for the "Evacuation - help us get away!" state award category through collaborating with other participants to ideate and produce a mobile web application using publicly available datasets.

Volunteer March 2016

Coder Dojo Brisbane (Australia)

Along with other team members, taught high school students various coding basics and principles. The lessons were delivered on schedule and effectively with positive receptions from both students and parents.

# Other Certifications

#### 2020

**Advanced Google Analytics**, Google Analytics Academy **Google Tag Manager Fundamentals**, Google Analytics Academy

#### 2019

**15.071x The Analytics Edge**, MITx on edX **Google Analytics for Beginners**, Google Analytics Academy

#### **Hobbies and Interests**

Cooking, Coffee, Embroidery, Electronics